David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Writings, 1813-2009 and undated (bulk 1939-2009); 1939-2009; 45073; 1.000; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Bald Head: A History of Smith Island, 1813-1986 and undated (bulk 1976-1986); 1976-1986; 6707; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Drafts and Publication Information, 1979-1986; 6953; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Dough, Wynne, 1984-1985; 27711; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dough, Wynne)
      - Dough, Kitty - Jacket, 1979-1984; 27712; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dough, Kitty - Jacket)
      - Draft: Unidentified [2 folders], circa 1985; 27713; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft: Unidentified [2 folders])
      - Early Drafts [2 folders], 1984; 27714; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Early Drafts [2 folders])
      - Galley Proofs [3 folders], 1985; 27715; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Galley Proofs [3 folders])
      - Gift Copies, 1984-1985; 27716; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Gift Copies)
      - Harrington, Jim, 1981-1984; 27717; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harrington, Jim)
      - Index (Original Copy, Proofs, etc.) and Jacket Copy, 1985; 27718; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Index (Original Copy, Proofs, etc.) and Jacket Copy)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986; 27719; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Page Proofs - Preliminary Corrections (David Stick), 1985; 27720; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Page Proofs - Preliminary Corrections (David Stick))
      - Paste-Up, 23 November 1984; 27721; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Paste-Up)
      - Preface, 1984; 27722; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Preface)
      - Publishers, Miscellaneous, 1983-1984; 27723; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publishers, Miscellaneous)
      - Reader Comments (Harrington, Henderson, Messick), 1984; 27724; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reader Comments (Harrington, Henderson, Messick))
      - Reviews, 1985-1986; 27725; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reviews)
      - Storie-McOwen Publishers, 1983-1984; 27726; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Storie-McOwen Publishers)
      - Working Copy, Consolidating Suggested Revisions by Readers, 1984; 27727; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Working Copy, Consolidating Suggested Revisions by Readers)
  - Cape Hatteras Seashore, 1964; 6708; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Sales and Promotions, 1964; 27728; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sales and Promotions)
    - Correspondence and Meetings, 1964; 27729; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence and Meetings)
    - Writing, circa 1964; 27730; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Writing)
    - Bruce Roberts Photograph, circa 1964; 27731; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bruce Roberts Photograph)
  - Currituck Doctor, 1918-1991 (bulk 1988-1992); 1988-1992; 6709; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    Currituck Doctor was a project begun by David Stick in the late 1980s to write a biography of Dr. Charles N. Wright, a medical doctor active in Currituck County in the mid-20th century. Stick recorded extensive oral history interviews with Wright as well as members of his family and people who worked in his practice. He also wrote a nearly complete draft of the book, but the book was never published due to ongoing disputes with the Wright family regarding ownership and intellectual property rights surrounding the interviews and the work itself. This subseries contains drafts of the book, correspondence with members of the Wright family and their legal representatives regarding ownership of the work (see folder: Wright Mess, 1990-1992), and research materials collected by David Stick, including oral history interviews, clippings, and a Wright family photo album. In his interviews, Wright discusses the history of medicine in rural Currituck County, including treatments he administered for issues related to reproductive and sexual health, such as pregnancy, masturbation, and sexual intercourse. Some of the descriptions are detailed and graphic.
    - C.N. Wright Clippings [1949-1970s], circa 1989; 27732; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder C.N. Wright Clippings [1949-1970s])
    - Drafts: Early/Preliminary [2 folders], 1989-1990; 27733; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Drafts: Early/Preliminary [2 folders])
    - Draft 1, January 1990; 27734; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 1)
    - Draft 1: Mary's Notes, 1990; 27735; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 1: Mary's Notes)
    - Draft 2, March 1990; 27736; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2)
    - Draft 2: Barry's Notes, 1990; 27737; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2: Barry's Notes)
    - Draft 2: Mary's Notes, 1990; 27738; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2: Mary's Notes)
    - Draft 2: Master Copy, 1990; 27739; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2: Master Copy)
    - Draft 3, July 1990; 27740; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 3)
    - Draft 4, August 1990; 27741; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 4)
    - History of Medicine in Currituck County by Dr. C.N. Wright (1973), circa 1989; 27742; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder History of Medicine in Currituck County by Dr. C.N. Wright (1973))
    - Interviews, 1988-1989; 6954; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Armstrong, Jeannette, 1989; 27743; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Armstrong, Jeannette)
      - Crabtree, Margie, 1989; 27744; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Crabtree, Margie)
      - Crutchley, William, 1989; 27745; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Crutchley, William)
      - Harris, Mike and Melody, 1989; 27746; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harris, Mike and Melody)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989; 27747; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Romm, Norma and William, 1989; 27748; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Romm, Norma and William)
      - Sawyer, Maxine, 1989; 27749; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sawyer, Maxine)
      - Waldrop, Lima, 1989; 27750; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Waldrop, Lima)
      - Wall, Grace, 1989; 27751; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wall, Grace)
      - Warren, Debbie, 1989; 27752; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Warren, Debbie)
      - Wright, John Jr., 1989; 27753; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright, John Jr.)
      - Wright, Virginia Caroline, 1989; 27754; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright, Virginia Caroline)
      - Recordings, 1988-1989; 7386; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Armstrong, Jeannette [audiocassette], 6 November 1989; 190669; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Armstrong, Jeannette [audiocassette])
        - Crabtree, Margie [audiocassette], 11 November 1989; 190670; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Crabtree, Margie [audiocassette])
        - Crutchley, Dr. William F. [audiocassette], 24 November 1989; 190671; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Crutchley, Dr. William F. [audiocassette])
        - Harris, Mike and Melody [audiocassette], 30 October 1989; 190672; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Harris, Mike and Melody [audiocassette])
        - Sawyer, Maxine and John Van Sant [audiocassette], 16 November 1989; 190673; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Sawyer, Maxine and John Van Sant [audiocassette])
        - Wall, Grace [audiocassette], 26 October 1989; 190674; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wall, Grace [audiocassette])
        - Warren, Debbie [audiocassette], 26 October 1989; 190675; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Warren, Debbie [audiocassette])
        - Wright, Caroline [audiocassette], 10 November 1989; 190676; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wright, Caroline [audiocassette])
        - Wright, Dr. Charles N. [audiocassette], August 1988; 190677; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wright, Dr. Charles N. [audiocassette])
        - Wright, Dr. Charles N. [VHS], August 1988; 190878; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wright, Dr. Charles N. [VHS])
        - Wright, John Jr. [audiocassette], 2 November 1989; 190678; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wright, John Jr. [audiocassette])
        - Wright, Pauline [audiocassette], 11 November 1989; 190679; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Wright, Pauline [audiocassette])
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991; 27755; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1989; 27756; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Notes)
    - Narrative Transcript of Charles Wright Interview by Kay Kenan, 1989; 27757; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Narrative Transcript of Charles Wright Interview by Kay Kenan)
    - Obituaries, C.N. Wright, 1989; 27758; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Obituaries, C.N. Wright)
    - Reproductions of Wright Family Photographs (Negatives and Contact Sheets), 1989; 27759; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reproductions of Wright Family Photographs (Negatives and Contact Sheets))
    - Substitute Pages and Revisions, 1990; 27760; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Substitute Pages and Revisions)
    - Unused Notes from Interviews, circa 1990; 27761; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unused Notes from Interviews)
    - Unused Quotes etc. to be Reviewed, circa 1989; 27762; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unused Quotes etc. to be Reviewed)
    - Wright Family Photo Album [2 folders], 1918-1988; 27763; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Family Photo Album [2 folders])
    - Wright Mess, 1990-1992; 29661; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Mess)
  - Dare County: A History [3 folders], 1969-1970; 6710; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County: A History [3 folders])
  - Early Writings (pre-1949), 1939-1950; 6711; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The Early Writings series, 1939-1950, contains articles, columns, short stories, and other pieces authored by Stick prior to the publication of his first book, Fabulous Dare, in 1949. Included in this series are papers related to Stick's tenure as associate editor of American Legion Magazine, an article on Toby Tillett and his Oregon Inlet ferry service, and correspondence and drafts of an article Stick wrote on goggle fishing. Columns contributed by Stick to various publications while he was in high school and college can be found in the Education subseries of the Personal papers series. Military writings can be found in the Military Service Subseries.
    - Agent: Lurton Blassingame, 1947-1950; 27764; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Agent: Lurton Blassingame)
    - Agent: Curtis Brown Ltd., 1947-1949; 27765; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Agent: Curtis Brown Ltd.)
    - American Legion Magazine, 1945-1948; 6955; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Articles, circa 1946-1947; 27766; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Articles)
      - Cartoons, 1946-1948; 27767; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cartoons)
      - Editor's Corner, 1946-1947; 27768; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Editor's Corner)
      - Form Letters, 1945-1946; 27769; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Form Letters)
      - General, 1946-1947; 27770; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder General)
      - Market Articles, 1946; 27771; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Market Articles)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947; 27772; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1945-1947; 27773; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Correspondence)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1946; 27774; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Personal Correspondence)
      - Personal Publicity, 1945-1946; 27775; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Personal Publicity)
      - Staff Memos, etc., 1946-1947; 27776; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Staff Memos, etc.)
    - Article Ideas, 1946-1948; 27777; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Article Ideas)
    - Articles: Correspondence, Accepted, 1945-1946; 27778; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Articles: Correspondence, Accepted)
    - Cartoon Anthology Book, 1946-1947; 27779; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cartoon Anthology Book)
    - Goggle Fishing Article Idea, 1939; 27780; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Goggle Fishing Article Idea)
    - Humor, circa 1940s; 27781; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Humor)
    - Ideas, circa 1940s; 27782; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ideas)
    - Little Miss Lovely Toes: Fiction, 1947-1948; 27783; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Little Miss Lovely Toes: Fiction)
    - Old Man Sheepshead Article, 1946; 27784; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Old Man Sheepshead Article)
    - Quarter Century of Ferry-Boating [Article on Toby Tillett], 1949; 27785; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Quarter Century of Ferry-Boating [Article on Toby Tillett])
    - Sample Rejection Slips, 1948-1950; 27786; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sample Rejection Slips)
    - Spear Fishing (Pic) Article, 1947-1948; 27787; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Spear Fishing (Pic) Article)
    - Unidentified Articles, 1945-1947; 27788; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Articles)
    - Unsold Short Stories, Late 1940s; 27789; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unsold Short Stories)
  - Fabulous Dare, 1947-1957; 6712; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - First Printing Miscellaneous, 1949-1952; 27790; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder First Printing Miscellaneous)
    - Copyright, 1948-1949; 27791; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Copyright)
    - Edwards and Broughton Co., 1949-1953; 27792; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Edwards and Broughton Co.)
    - Expenses and Bills, 1949-1950; 27793; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Expenses and Bills)
    - Acknowledgements, Complimentary Copies, 1949-1950; 27794; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Acknowledgements, Complimentary Copies)
    - Finances - Loans, 1949-1951; 27795; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Finances - Loans)
    - Duplicate Reviews, 1949; 27796; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Duplicate Reviews)
    - Lost Colony Notes and References, 1947-1948; 27797; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lost Colony Notes and References)
    - Loose Correspondence and Notes, 1947-1957; 27798; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose Correspondence and Notes)
    - Lucky Dare (First Draft), circa 1948; 27799; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lucky Dare (First Draft))
    - Second Script, circa 1949; 27800; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Second Script)
    - Clippings, 1949-1950; 27801; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Clippings)
    - Reprint Material, 1953-1954; 27802; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reprint Material)
  - Graveyard of the Atlantic, 1913-1979 (bulk 1950-1952); 1950-1952; 6713; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Research Material, 1913-1967; 6956; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Additional Wrecks Index [Folders 1 and 2 of 6], circa 1950; 27803; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Additional Wrecks Index [Folders 1 and 2 of 6])
      - Additional Wrecks Index [Folders 3-6], circa 1950; 27804; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Additional Wrecks Index [Folders 3-6])
      - Correspondence: Libraries, 1950-1951; 27805; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence: Libraries)
      - Interviews, etc., 1951; 27806; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Interviews, etc.)
      - Mariner's Museum, 1951-1953; 27807; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Mariner's Museum)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1952; 27808; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - National Archives and Library of Congress, circa 1950; 27809; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Archives and Library of Congress)
      - Notes, Miscellaneous, circa 1950; 27810; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes, Miscellaneous)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks - Bill Harris from Signal Corps Journals, 1967; 27811; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks - Bill Harris from Signal Corps Journals)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks - Chronological, 1526-1852, circa 1950; 27812; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks - Chronological, 1526-1852)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks - Chronological, 1853-1871, circa 1950; 27813; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks - Chronological, 1853-1871)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Ciabo and Paraguay, 1927; 27814; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Ciabo and Paraguay)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Florida, 1913-1917, circa 1950; 27815; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Florida)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Huron, circa 1950; 27816; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Huron)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Hydro Card List, Metropolis, Home, Pulaski, circa 1950; 27817; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Hydro Card List, Metropolis, Home, Pulaski)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Metropolis, circa 1950; 27818; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Metropolis)
      - Notes: Shipwrecks, Pulaski, circa 1950; 27819; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: Shipwrecks, Pulaski)
      - Notes: U-Boat Activity, 1918, circa 1950; 27820; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes: U-Boat Activity, 1918)
      - Reports of Wrecks and Assistance Rendered by the U.S. Lifesaving Service, Cape Henry to Charleston, 1876-1914, 1952; 27821; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports of Wrecks and Assistance Rendered by the U.S. Lifesaving Service, Cape Henry to Charleston, 1876-1914)
      - U.S. Government, 1950-1954; 27822; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder U.S. Government)
      - World Almanac/New York World Telegram Correspondence, 1951; 27823; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder World Almanac/New York World Telegram Correspondence)
    - Drafts and Publication Information, 1950-1979; 6957; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Correspondence: Brown, Aycock, 1951-1952; 27824; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence: Brown, Aycock)
      - Correspondence: Readers, 1952-1954; 27825; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence: Readers)
      - Cowles, Porter, 1952-1957; 27826; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cowles, Porter)
      - Davis, Lambert, 1951-1957; 27827; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Davis, Lambert)
      - Draft 1 [2 folders], circa 1952; 27828; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 1 [2 folders])
      - Draft 2 [2 folders], circa 1952; 27829; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 2 [2 folders])
      - Draft 3 [Folder 1 of 2], circa 1952; 27830; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 3 [Folder 1 of 2])
      - Draft 3 [Folder 2 of 2], circa 1952; 27831; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft 3 [Folder 2 of 2])
      - Draft: Final, circa 1952; 27832; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft: Final)
      - Draft: Various Chapters, circa 1952; 27833; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft: Various Chapters)
      - Draft: Chapter - Pulaski and Dunbar Davis, 1951; 27834; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft: Chapter - Pulaski and Dunbar Davis)
      - Duffey, Gwen, 1951-1954; 27835; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Duffey, Gwen)
      - Front Matter, Notes, etc., circa 1952; 27836; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Front Matter, Notes, etc.)
      - Index, circa 1952; 27837; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Index)
      - List of Vessels Probably Lost on the North Carolina Coast, 1952; 27838; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder List of Vessels Probably Lost on the North Carolina Coast)
      - Photographs and Illustrations, 1952-1953; 27839; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Photographs and Illustrations)
      - Publicity, 1952-1979; 27840; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publicity)
      - Reviews, 1952; 27841; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reviews)
      - Rewrites, September 1951; 27842; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rewrites)
      - Sales, 1952-1954; 27843; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sales)
      - UNC Press - Promotion [2 folders], 1951-1957; 27844; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Press - Promotion [2 folders])
      - UNC Press - Miscellaneous, 1951-1958; 27845; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Press - Miscellaneous)
      - Writing Expenses, 1950-1953; 27846; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Writing Expenses)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1955-2006; 6714; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Letters to the Editor)
  - Man's Harbor, 1932 and undated; 6715; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    Man's Harbor was a fictional work set on North Carolina's Outer Banks at the time of colonization in the late 16th century. The book was never published. This subseries contains drafts of the novel.
    - First Complete Draft, Part 1, undated; 27847; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder First Complete Draft, Part 1)
    - First Complete Draft, Part 2, undated; 27848; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder First Complete Draft, Part 2)
    - Second Draft, undated; 27849; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Second Draft)
    - Third Draft (to Agent), undated; 27850; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Third Draft (to Agent))
    - Finished Manuscript, Part 1, undated; 27851; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Finished Manuscript, Part 1)
    - First Half, Copy, undated; 27852; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder First Half, Copy)
    - Jamaican Draft, Part 1, undated; 27853; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Jamaican Draft, Part 1)
    - Unidentified Draft, Part 1, undated; 27854; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Draft, Part 1)
    - Unidentified Draft, Part 2, undated; 27855; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Draft, Part 2)
    - Notes, 1932 and undated; 27856; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes)
    - Introduction, undated; 27857; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Introduction)
    - Part 1, Original, undated; 27858; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 1, Original)
    - Part 1, Rewrite, undated; 27859; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Part 1, Rewrite)
    - Parts 2-4, undated; 27860; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Parts 2-4)
    - Appendix, undated; 27861; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Appendix)
    - Extra Pages, undated; 27862; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Extra Pages)
  - Musings of a Maverick, 2002-circa 2004; 6958; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Musings, circa 2002; 27863; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Musings)
    - More Musings, circa 2004; 27864; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder More Musings)
    - Draft, circa 2002; 27865; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Draft)
    - Final Draft for Printing Less Photographs [2 Folders], 2002; 27866; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Final Draft for Printing Less Photographs [2 Folders])
    - Annotated Draft [2 Folders], circa 2002; 27867; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Annotated Draft [2 Folders])
    - Final Version, 2002; 27868; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Final Version)
  - Narratives, 1960-1997; 6959; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    David Stick's Narratives consisted of 33 short narratives describing the history of the numerous organizations and agencies with which Stick was involved over the course of his life, primarily written from the documentation of each organization found in the Organizations and Agencies series of this collection. This work was originally begun under the title A Half Century of Observations in the 1970s, then revised by Stick in the 1990s. The work was never published. This subseries contains drafts of the narratives, including early iterations of Stick's Half Century of Observations, notes, and correspondence with Wynne Dough, who advised Stick on the project.
    - A Half Century of Observations, 1978; 27869; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A Half Century of Observations)
    - A Half Century of Observations (Background for Future Narratives), 1977-1978; 27870; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A Half Century of Observations (Background for Future Narratives))
    - A Half Century of Observations Original Manuscript, 1978; 27871; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A Half Century of Observations Original Manuscript)
    - Genesis of OBRA [Outer Banks Recreation Association], 1960-circa 1980s; 27872; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Genesis of OBRA [Outer Banks Recreation Association])
    - Outer Banks Community Foundation, 1989; 27873; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Community Foundation)
    - AFHAC [America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Commission], circa 1987; 27874; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder AFHAC [America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Commission])
    - Chicamacomico Historical Association, 1991; 27875; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicamacomico Historical Association)